[
  {
    "id": "71",
    "question": "Which statement describes a characteristic of AWS Lambda?",
    "options": [
      "Lambda runs code only when it is activated by an event and uses only the compute resources that are needed.",
      "A developer's methods and configuration options for ensuring high availability with Lambda are similar to their approach with Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2).",
      "Lambda functions run in on-demand, temporary environments, and the developer controls when new environments are created or shut down.",
      "A developer must write Lambda functions that use one of the runtimes that the Lambda service provides."
    ],
    "answer": [0],
    "module": "Module 7"
  },
  {
    "id": "72",
    "question": "Which constraint cannot be modified?",
    "options": [
      "Function timeout",
      "Reserved concurrency",
      "Burst quota",
      "Regional quota"
    ],
    "answer": [2],
    "module": "Module 7"
  },
  {
    "id": "73",
    "question": "Which option describes how Amazon API Gateway invokes AWS Lambda?",
    "options": [
      "API Gateway directly invokes a function with a synchronous invocation.",
      "Lambda processes API Gateway requests asynchronously and retries each request up to two times.",
      "Lambda uses an event source mapping and polls API Gateway for requests.",
      "API Gateway directly invokes a function and retries the request until it succeeds or expires."
    ],
    "answer": [0],
    "module": "Module 7"
  },
  {
    "id": "74",
    "question": "Which actions require permissions that are defined in the AWS Lambda execution role? (Select TWO.)",
    "options": [
      "A Lambda function writes to an Amazon S3 bucket.",
      "A Lambda function reads from an Amazon DynamoDB table.",
      "A Lambda function creates log groups.",
      "A Lambda function deletes CloudWatch Logs.",
      "A Lambda function writes logs to CloudWatch Logs."
    ],
    "answer": [0, 2],
    "module": "Module 7"
  },
  {
    "id": "75",
    "question": "Which AWS Lambda deployment option should be used?",
    "options": [
      "Copy the code into the Lambda console editor to create and deploy the function.",
      "Upload a .zip file of the code to create and deploy the function.",
      "Use the AWS CLI to deploy the function directly from the developer's machine.",
      "Create a deployment package that includes the code and dependencies, and upload it to an Amazon S3 bucket."
    ],
    "answer": [0],
    "module": "Module 7"
  },
  {
    "id": "76",
    "question": "Which issue might be addressed by adding provisioned concurrency to an AWS Lambda function?",
    "options": [
      "Another Lambda function runs in the same account and Region. It sometimes spikes and consumes all available concurrency, causing the function to fail.",
      "An application that uses the Lambda function responds slowly for the first few users who sign in each day. Lambda metrics show higher latency for those initial requests.",
      "A legacy backend system fails intermittently when the developer connects to it. To avoid extra costs, they want to reduce the function's wait time when the backend fails.",
      "The developer wants more visibility into transactions that use the Lambda function to identify bottlenecks."
    ],
    "answer": [1],
    "module": "Module 7"
  },
  {
    "id": "77",
    "question": "Which AWS Lambda configuration setting might a developer use to manage function errors when configuring an Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) topic as the event source for a Lambda function? (Select TWO.)",
    "options": [
      "State machines",
      "File systems",
      "Destinations",
      "Virtual private cloud",
      "Asynchronous invocations"
    ],
    "answer": [2, 4],
    "module": "Module 7"
  },
  {
    "id": "78",
    "question": "A zipped deployment package including code and custom libraries is 75 MB in size. Which AWS Lambda deployment option should be used?",
    "options": [
      "Copy the code into the Lambda console editor to create and deploy the function.",
      "Upload a .zip file from an integrated development environment (IDE) to load the deployment package directly into the Lambda console.",
      "Upload the deployment package to an Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) bucket, and specify the bucket name and object key on the Lambda console.",
      "Upload the deployment package to an Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) volume, and use the File Systems configuration to reference it."
    ],
    "answer": [2],
    "module": "Module 7"
  },
  {
    "id": "79",
    "question": "A function's Amazon Resource Name (ARN) is as follows: arn:aws:lambda:aws-region:acct-id:function:helloworld:PROD Which statement about this function is correct, based on its ARN?",
    "options": [
      "This ARN will invoke the immutable PROD version of the function.",
      "This ARN will invoke the version of the function that is currently associated with the PROD alias.",
      "This ARN will invoke the function and include the AWS Lambda layer that is named PROD.",
      "This ARN will deploy the helloworld function into the PROD account."
    ],
    "answer": [1],
    "module": "Module 7"
  },
  {
    "id": "70",
    "question": "Users of a serverless application have reported errors that occur when they try to retrieve order information. Assuming that AWS X-Ray is enabled, what is the first step the developer might take in X-Ray to start troubleshooting the reported issues quickly?",
    "options": [
      "Drill down into the most recent traces to look for errors.",
      "Search for metadata that is related to the users who are reporting issues.",
      "Add annotations that the developer can use to start grouping and filtering traces.",
      "Use the service map to visually locate errors across the application."
    ],
    "answer": [3],
    "module": "Module 7"
  }
]
